[{"answer": "Welcome to my friend. May we meet your filing needs", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Please have a seat, Mr. my friend..", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You're a fag or a liar", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " I mean, I am really attracted to you. my friend, you are a fag. We can share recipes, if you like, my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Nah. I'm not hungry. I'm sorry I didn't call. It was just, you know, hard to get away", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'm sorry. How was your evening", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hi. my friend! What're you up to in this vacant office", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " That's right, my friend, it is against floor policy, but as long as you're here, let me tell you what I know about our cute little door friend. Many years ago, this very office was occupied by a kindly old watchmaker named Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend..", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yes, of course. He's a celebrity", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Tickets to my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Fine. I'll do it myself. I was going to offer a partnership to you, but this way it's more money for me", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Sure. It'd be fun", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What, are you nuts? That's Oprah talking", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "This is absurd. Besides my friend's an allergist. If you're going to do something, do it right", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Long term psychic or physiological repercussions", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Can I be anyone I want", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No. Don't be an ass", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You can be my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No they're not", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You've always loved the animals", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Oh my darling. Oh my sweetheart", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Are you torturing me on purpose", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I don't think so. I've fallen in love. This is what people who've fallen in love look like", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Holy shit, yes", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Holy shit! He said what I said", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Holy shit, yes", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Holy shit! He said what I said", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Something was making me talk. Some Goddamn thing was making me move. I gotta get out of here", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No, Dollface, I know what my passion taking hold feels like. I gotta go", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "my friend.  my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You fell in love with her first", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You didn't do anything about it out of respect for the fact that she wouldn't let you near her with a ten foot pole, which is, by the way, about nine feet, nine inches off the mark anyway", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " Really? Well, you know, he's quite good. I'm surprised. Anyway, I have a session with my friend I have to attend. I'll speak with you soon", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I thought so too, doll. I guess we were mistaken", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I suppose I could come to him in a dream. I don't know. That's the best I can think of right now", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "No, a sexy dream. Of course, a scary dream", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Bad dream, darling", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "You've got to be kidding", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " Hello, my friend. I saw your show", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Yeah, I saw the", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "It's my job to ask the questions. Yours to answer them", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Says me. Do you dream often", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Says who", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Do you", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "The monkey", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "A better friend", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "People make mistakes", "docId": "Being-John-Malkovich.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "I know", "qsentId": 54}]